ipaidabribe.com 2014-05-28

# Privacy Policy

Please remember that this website is a platform for you to post your reports and comment on other posts on the website. Whilst we, at I Paid A Bribe, welcome all viewpoints, we request you to submit constructive inputs.

Users are responsible for all content posted by them and the website shall not be responsible for the accuracy, legality or decency of any material posted by users on the pages of this website. Please do not post messages that are false, defamatory, abusive, threatening, harmful, obscene, or profane. A defamatory comment is a false comment that is capable of damaging the reputation of a person or organization. If successfully sued in relation to any content posted by you, you could be held liable for considerable damages and costs.

By using this website, you consent to our collection and use of information relating to your use of the website as described in this Privacy Policy. We do not collect, use or disclose your personal information for any purpose other than as detailed below, to further or promote the objectives of IPaidABribe or our other projects.

We are committed to protecting your privacy as a visitor to our website and take the privacy of your information very seriously.

**1.              ****INFORMATION COLLECTION:**

When you visit the site you may provide two types of information: (a) personal information that you knowingly choose to disclose, and which is collected on an individual basis; and (b) website use information collected on an aggregate basis as you and other users browse the website.

**1.1.           ****Personal Information**

You may post reports, perform searches and queries, share and transmit information and use the interactive features of the website. You may provide us with your email address by registering for updates on the website.

We receive different types of information about you including information that is required when you submit a report, actual information posted by you, as well as personal information that you may choose to share publicly.

Choosing to make your information public means anyone, including people who are not users of the website, will be able to see your public information. Choosing to make your information public also means that such information can be associated with you. Please note that in the event you choose to make your details ‘visible publicly’, your details will be visible on the website and publicly accessible to one and all.    

**1.2.           ****Website Use Information**

Similar to other websites, this website utilizes a standard technology called ‘cookies’ and server logs and may collect information about how the website is used by you.

A cookie is a very small text document which often includes an anonymous unique identifier. When you visit a website, that site’s computer seeks certain electronic, automated permissions from your computer, to store this file in a part of your hard drive specifically designated for cookies. Each website can send its own cookie to your browser if your browser’s preferences allow it.

Information gathered through cookies and server logs may include the date and time of visits, the pages viewed, the time spent on our website, and the websites visited just before and just after the website.

As you use the website, the website uses its cookies to differentiate you from other users so your preferences are unique to you. In some cases, the website also uses cookies to prevent you from seeing unnecessary advertisements or requiring you to log in more than is necessary for security. Cookies, in conjunction with our server log files, allow us to calculate the aggregate number of people visiting our website and parts of the website which are most popular with our users. This helps us gather feedback in order to constantly improve the website and our services. Cookies do not allow us to gather any personal information about you and we do not generally store any personal information that you provide to us, in your cookies.

Please note that, to protect your privacy, your browser will only permit a website to access the cookies it has already sent to you, not the cookies sent to you by other websites. This means, neither can our website access cookies sent to you by other websites, nor can other websites access or recognize cookies sent by our website to your computer.

**2.          ****SHARING YOUR INFORMATION WITH THIRD PARTIES:**

We will not share any information provided by you, without your express consent, with any third parties, except as detailed hereinbelow.

Whilst filing a report, you have various options, such as requesting that the report be sent to the senior officials of a department, to the Lokayukta or State Vigilance Department Central Vigilance Commission, or choosing to share your story with the media. In all the above instances, you may be required to share your name and contact details. Please note that a validation email will be sent to your email address, for your confirmation, before we undertake any action on the request submitted by you, in this regard.

Your trust is important to us, which is why we do not share information we have received about you unless (i) we have received your permission, given your notice such as by telling you about it in this policy; or (ii) have removed your name or any other personally identifying information from any content posted by you. We provide your information to third parties only after we have removed your name or any other personally identifying information from it, or have combined it with other people’s data in a way that the resultant data is no longer associated with you.

We do not share any information collected through cookies, as detailed above, with any third parties.

We may be required to disclose information relating to your use of the website under applicable law or if we believe that such action is necessary to (a) conform to the law or comply with legal process served upon us; (b) protect and defend our rights and property, the website, and/or the users of the website; or (c) act under circumstances to protect the safety of users of this website, our security or that of third parties.

**3.          ****SECURITY FOR YOUR DATA:**

We will take all the appropriate precautions and the requisite security measures that are technically feasible to protect your information to prevent any unauthorized use, loss, misuse or alteration/abuse of your information. We may use the information we receive about you as part of our efforts to keep the website safe and secure, for internal operations including troubleshooting, data analysis, testing, research and service improvement. In any case, we restrict access of your personal information to select employees who need to know this information in order to operate, develop or improve our services, and who are bound by non-disclosure agreements in respect of such information.

**4.          ****THIRD PARTY LINKS:**

This website may contain links to third party websites that are not controlled by Janaagraha. These third party links are available to you as a convenience and you agree to use these links at your own risk. Please be aware that neither IPaidABribe nor Janaagraha is responsible for the practices employed by third party websites linked to IPaidABribe or content contained therein.

Often hyperlinks to other websites are provided solely as pointers to information on topics that may be useful to the users of the website.  Please remember that when you use a link to go from our website to another web site, this Privacy Policy is no longer in effect. Your browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which contain further links, is subject to that third party website’s own rules and policies and we have no liability whatsoever, in such circumstances.

**5.          ****CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY:**

This Privacy Policy is effective as of 11th February, 2013. In the event we change our Privacy Policy and procedures, we will post those changes on the website to keep you aware of what information we collect, how such information is used and under what circumstances we may disclose it.

However, changes to the privacy policy may be made without prior notice, and by accessing this website you are deemed to be aware of the new/changed Privacy Policy; and to have consented to the same. You are requested to regularly visit this page to update yourself of the current and prevailing Privacy Policy.

**Note** : Please do not post fraudulent or defamatory reports for which you may be liable. If a law enforcement agency challenges such report, we will be required to share your IP address.

If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, or wish to update any of the information you have provided to us, please contact our representative at [ipab@janaagraha.org](mailto:ipab@janaagraha.org).
